Casey O'Keefe

Full Stack Developer

ocase1990@gmail.com 512-738-4987 ocase1990.github.io www.linkedin.com/in/caseyokeefe512

About Me

I am a dependable, hard working, goal oriented, and determined person. When placed in a role in any environment I strive to make the biggest impact I can. To ensure myself above competency I strive to consume information daily and focus on contributing to the team in the most efficient way. I freelance projects weekly and I am ready to contribute to a team.

Skills

Languages & Frameworks: JavaScript ES6 / ES7, React & Redux, React Native, Express, Node.js,

MongoDB /Mongoose, jQuery, HTML/CSS(SCSS)/Bootstrap 3 / 4, Python, Wordpress

Features: Stripe, Webpac Module Bundler

Website Design: Experienced in website development from consultation to deployment. **Development Best Practices:** Disciplined usage of Git to properly organize project workflow. **Management:** Management experience of over 20 people at a time. Various customer interactions

throughout career with public service or private service situations.

Other: Extensive knowledge of Excel including harvesting data, creating tables, charts, and interactive Excel Dashboards. Firm grasp on programs such as Photoshop and text editors.

Experience

Austin Coding Academy Assistant Instructor January 2018 - Present

- Assistant instructor teaching students in various levels of coding classes.
- --Assisting students in a 10 week intensive coding class of approximately 20 students at a time.
- --Tutoring cohorts through introductory HTML/CSS and JavaScript.
- --Using multiple methods to teach students including in class and remote.

Chat With Me

November 2017 - December 2017

Creator

React Native Chat app utilizing firebase storage.

- --Chat app created with React Native to chat with other users based on topic of the conversation.
- --Compatible with Android or iOS.

Hideout Coffee House / Theatre Website

March 2017 - June 2017

Co-Creator

Redesigned the website utilizing current HTML/CSS/JavaScript with over 30 pages of content.

- --I designed the restructure and wireframe and delegated tasks to my other two team members who were involved.
- --Organized meetings with customer for initial design and redesigns.
- --Took and updated images/videos on website.

Williamson County

February 2010 - May 2014

Paramedic

- -- Worked in a county Jail and 911 EMS environment responding to non-emergent and emergent situations.
- -- Interacting with thousands of people of the public and families per year.
- -- Maintaining skills with continuing education.
- -- Spearheading projects and development for new training methods and new ways to outreach to the public.

Casey O'Keefe

Full Stack Developer

ocase1990@gmail.com 512-738-4987 ocase1990.github.io www.linkedin.com/in/caseyokeefe512

Sonic Drive In June 2016 - June 2019

Manager

- -- Promoted to manager after 1 year of work.
- -- Opened/ Closed store daily while managing up to 20 employees at a time.
- -- Interacting with hundreds of customers daily to improve customer service.
- -- Managed food/ inventory stock shipments.

Education Austin Coding Academy 2017

Full Stack Web Development

Austin Community College 2010

Associates of Science in Paramedicine 3.5GPA